Friends, Reliance Industries has
presented its quarterly figures,
so let's also see how the
quarterly figures of Reliance Industries have come
and whether any
announcements were seen by the company, as
you can see, let's
first quickly see how its quarterly
results have come, after that we will see whether any
announcements have been seen,
so here you will see that we will
discuss its console date financial
results, the total value given is given
in Rs crores, here
you will see Hiranid and here you can see quadrant,
if we talk about total
income or total revenue, then this time the
total income that we have seen is
₹ 29900 sorry ₹ 219294 crores, whereas
in the previous quarter it was 2 lakh
23739 crores, so the
revenue has seen a growth since the previous quarter, and
if we talk about Kari Heroin, then there is a
great  There has been a
great jump in its profit and income. We will compare it with the previous year, but keep
in mind that the revenue in the quarter has declined. There
you will see that the expenses, that is, the total expenditure
of the company this time is
₹195,214 crore (211 crores), whereas
in the previous quarter it was ₹2,733 crores. So,
its expenses have reduced significantly this time compared to the previous quarter. This is a
very good thing. Taking this out
and looking at Heroin,
you will see that there is a dangerous
jam in the expenses there too. But
you will see that the revenue has been excellent this time.
You will see that in the previous quarter, sorry, the
revenue is lower than the previous quarter. But
you will see that the income and
expenses are higher this time. So, it means that the company has made a
profit again.
Let us see how much profit it has made. Now,
if I talk about net profit per day period,
you will see that the profit per day period is
21327.  There was a profit of crores whereas
in the previous quarter there was a profit of 178006 crores then
why is there so much difference in the profit
because brother you will see that the profit that has been made is
due to expenditure, the expenditure has
reduced, that is why whereas
in the previous quarter the expenditure was more, the revenue was
also more but the expenditure has reduced this time, the
revenue has reduced a little bit, okay no
problem but the expenditure, then let me move on to the
profit and you will see on Heroin reverse,
there is also a great performance, so
its quarter four
numbers which are quite excellent have been seen, so
from here the stock is going to see even more growth,
if I
talk about it, then some
announcement was made by it, so here you people should
pause its video and read this note
in detail, I hope you liked the video, if you
liked the video then like it, if you have
not subscribed to the channel then do not
forget to subscribe and thank you for
watching the video